[
  {
    "question": "1. ADO.NET stands for ?",
    choice1: "ActiveX Data Object",
    choice2: "All Data Object",
    choice3: "Access Data Object",
    choice4: " ActiveX DataSet Object",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "The DataReader object is an alternative to the?",
    "choice1": "Dataset",
    "choice2": "DataAdapter",
    "choice3": "Both 1 and 2",
    "choice4": "None of above",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question":"Syntax for closing and opening the connection in ADO.net is _______________",
    "choice1": "sqlConn.Open() and sqlConn.close()",
    "choice2": "sqlConn.open() and sqlConn.Close()",
    "choice3": "sqlConn.Open() and sqlConn.Close()",
    "choice4": "None of the above",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question":"The main features of dotConnect for SQL Server includes ___________",
    "choice1": " Extra data binding capabilities",
    "choice2": "Ability of monitoring query execution",
    "choice3": "Supports the latest versions of SQL Server",
    "choice4": "All Of the above",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which properties Returns the parent DataSet?",
    "choice1": "ParentColumns",
    "choice2": "ParentRelations",
    "choice3": "ParentDataSet",
    "choice4": "DataSet",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the extensionfor Asp.net page?",
    "choice1": ".asp",
    "choice2": ".aspx",
    "choice3": ".asx",
    "choice4": ".apx",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "MVC stands for ____.",
    "choice1": "Model Vocal Controller ",
    "choice2": "Mode View Controller",
    "choice3": "Model View Count",
    "choice4": "Model View Controller",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the correct basic syntax of Application directive?",
    "choice1": "<%@ Application Language='C#' %>",
    "choice2": "<!-- Application Language='C#' --> ",
    "choice3": "<%@ Application_DIR Language='C#' %>",
    "choice4": "<%@ DIR @Application Language='C#' %>",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which protocol is used to call a web service?",
    "choice1": "SOAP Protocol",
    "choice2": "HTTP Protocol",
    "choice3": "TCP Protocol",
    "choice4": "FTP Protocol",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the default timeout for a cookie in ASP.Net?",
    "choice1": "10 Minutes",
    "choice2": "20Minutes",
    "choice3": "5Minutes",
    "choice4": "30Minutes",
    "answer": 4
  }
]